Guide to the Washington Metro Oral History Project collection, 1975-2021 MS2214
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Interview transcripts and notes, MS2214 Series 2; 0.50 Linear feet
  This series contains transcripts of oral history interviews conducted by Zachary Schrag. It also includes notes taken by Zachary Schrag during these interviews.
  Link for uploaded interviews
  There are transcripts for a small portion of these oral histories. These are available in the Internet Archive. Material from this collection can be found at https://archive.org/details/gwulibraries?sort=titleSorter&&and[]=subject%3A%22MS2214%22
  - Cleatus Barnett, 2001 January 25 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - Alan Boyd, 2001 October 02 (Box 8, Item 2)
  - Richard Chenoweth transcript (coming soon), 2021 August 21; MS2214 Series 2
  - Peter Craig, 1999 November 05 (Box 8, Item 3)
  - William Gallagher (coming soon), 2021 July 21; MS2214 Series 2
  - Ivailo Karadimov and Jeffrey Winstel (coming soon), 2021 July 07; MS2214 Series 2
  - Cody Pfanstiehl, 1999 December 15 - 2000 September 20 (Box 8, Item 4)
    Three interviews: 12/15/1999, 01/04/2000, and 09/20/2000
  - Roberts Owen [1/2], 2000 July 19 (Box 8, Item 5)
  - Roberts Owen [2/2], 2000 July 19 (Box 8, Item 6)
    This transcript includes corrections made by Mr. Owen in April 2002
  - Barbara Richardson (coming soon), 2021 August 04; MS2214 Series 2; 1 item(s)
  - Joseph Saunders, 2000 September 11 (Box 8, Item 7)
  - Interview notes [1/2], undated (Box 8, Item 8)
    This folder includes notes taken by Zachary Schrag on his recorded interviews with various participants in the history of the Washington Metro. Excluded are those interviews for which verbatim transcripts exist.
  - Interview notes [2/2], undated (Box 8, Item 9)
  - Textual materials (notes and transcripts), undated (Box 9, Item 6)